### Contact

jennievartebedian@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jennievartebedian-8a32b185 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

CPR Certified
Health Education
Customer Service

#### Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support
Basic Life Support
NIH Stroke Scale
NICHE (Geriatric Resource Nurse)

# Jennie Vartebedian

Travel Registered Nurse at Aya Healthcare

Somerdale, New Jersey

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Customer Service, Communication, Organizational Development, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey-Camden.

## Experience

Aya Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
October 2019 - Present (9 months)

Southern Ocean Medical Center Travel Nurse January 2020 - Present (6 months) Manahawkin, New Jersey

Hackensack Meridian Health Travel Registered Nurse October 2019 - December 2019 (3 months) Brick, New Jersey

EvergreenHealth Travel Registered Nurse June 2019 - September 2019 (4 months) Kirkland, Washington

American Mobile Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
December 2017 - September 2019 (1 year 10 months)

KULA HOSPITAL
Travel Registered Nurse
February 2019 - May 2019 (4 months)

Jefferson Health New Jersey
Travel Registered Nurse
November 2018 - January 2019 (3 months)
Sewell, New Jersey

Med Surg Tele

Methodist Healthcare System Travel Registered Nurse April 2018 - July 2018 (4 months) San Antonio, Texas

Neurosciences

Vanderbilt Stallworth Rehabilitation Hospital Travel Registered Nurse December 2017 - March 2018 (4 months) Nashville, Tennessee

Jefferson Healthcare Registered Nurse April 2015 - November 2017 (2 years 8 months) Stratford, New Jersey

## Education

Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey-Camden Bachelor of Science in Nursing (2013 - 2014)

Monmouth University

Bachelor, Health Services/Allied Health/Health Sciences,

General · (2008 - 2013)